

# Yohey Kawabe

+81-80-3177-0925

yhykwb83@gmail.com

1-3-31 Sakurayama, Zushi, Kanagawa, 249-0005 JAPAN

## **Profile**

I began my career at Dentsu Inc., where I worked as a Producer/Planner/Copywriter for three years before being seconded for two years to the joint venture between Dentsu, Digital Garage, and ADK to help establish Twitter Japan. Upon returning to Dentsu, I transitioned to the role of Copywriter and Planner, earning recognition through advertising awards before departing in 2012. I then spent two years as Executive Officer at a newly launched digital content company under the Shogakukan Group. In 2014, I founded and led my own company, R, specializing in digital content production, managing the business for 10 years before its dissolution in 2023. Since January 2024, I have been with Honda Motor Co., Ltd. as part of the Corporate Planning Division and Creative Solutions Center

## Career

#### 2024 - Present at Honda Motor Co., Ltd.

2024 - Creative Solution Center in Honda Motor Co., Ltd.

2024 - 2024 Honda R&D Design Workshop in ICFF, New York

2024 - 2024 Honda R&D Exhibition "Dream Experiment"

#### 2014 - 2023 at R Inc.

2024 - 2024 NTT DX Partners Content Director

2020 - 2021 Omiya Bibli - Creative Director

2020 - 2022 Asics Japan Owned Media - Content Director

2019 - 2020 Kochi-Prefecture campaign Creative Director

2018 - 2020 Olympic Official SNS Account - Content Director

2016 - 2018 KANEBO (Cosmetic Brand) - Creative Director

2016 - 2017 LUMINE - Creative Director

2015 - 2018 TSS - Creative Director - Awarded

2014 - 2018 Instagram Japan - Official Account Editor

#### **Skills**

- -Branding
- -Creative Direction
- -Content Planning
- -Film Direction
- Art Direction
- Graphic Design
- -Editorial Design
- CopyWriting
- -Frontend Dev
- Mobile App Dev

# Language

- Japanese (Native)
- -English (Business)

#### Career

#### 2012 - 2014 at Shogakukan Inc.

2014 - 2017 SUBARU Official Website - Content Director

2013 - 2014 Benesse Corporation - Creative Director 2012 -

2013 Relux - Creative Director

#### 2007 - 2012 at Dentsu Inc.

2011 - 2012 BEAMS 35th Anniversary - Producer / Planner / Copy Writer - Awarded

2011 - 2012 TOKYU PLAZA OMOTESANDO HARAJUKU - Producer / Communication Planner 2011

- 2012 Suntory Beverage & Food Limited - Web Director (GREEN DAKARA / BOSS Coffee) 2010 -

2011 JINS Corporate Website Renewal - Producer / Content Planner

2010 - 2012 Twitter Japan - PR Planner (On loan to Digital Garage)

2009 - 2010 TOSHIBA CORPORATION - Digital Communication Planner

2009 - 2010 UNIQLO - Web Director (HEAT TECH Global Campaign)- Awarded 2008 -

2010 MARS Japan - Web Director (KalKan / Pedigree / Greenies / Snickers)

2007 - 2009 TOSHIBA CORPORATION - Web Director / Content Planner (White Goods)

2007 - 2010 Mizkan Group - Web Director / Content Planner (AJIPON)

and more

## **Awards**

2018 Top 100 - Good Design Award Japan

2017 Finalist - Blow-Up Art house Film Festival in Chicago, United States

2012 Representative of Tokyo Hub World Economic Forum U-33

2012 Finalist – Spike Asia Festival of Creativity Mobile App Div 2012

Bronze - Yahoo! JAPAN Creative Award Mobile App Div 2010 Silver -

Tokyo Interactive Ad Award Integrated Campaign div

# **Degrees**

2023 - 2023 Certificate of Software Engineering - General Assembly Malaysia (Programming)

2019 – 2022 Doctor of Education – Waseda University Grad School (Withdraw)

2017 - 2019 Master of Education - Yokohama National University Grad School (M.Ed)

2003 - 2007 Bachelor of Education - Tokyo Gakugei University (B.A.)

### **Scores**

TOEIC 850 / 990 (2023)